'use strict';
const data = [
  {
    question: 'Which of the following races is not available to players?',
    answers: ['Pixie','Simic Hybrid','Goblin','Tortle'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following classes is not available to players?',
    answers: ['Druid','Wizard','Sorcerer','Thief'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following races has the highest Intelligence bonus?',
    answers: ['Dragonborn','Gnome','Centaur','Elf'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following classes has the most Hit Die?',
    answers: ['Fighter','Monk','Cleric','Barbarian'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following races has the most number of subraces?',
    answers: ['Lizardfolk','Elf','Tiefling','Human'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following classes does not have Spellcasting as a base class feature?',
    answers: ['Warlock','Paladin','Bard','Ranger'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is an ability that measures a characterâ€™s reflexes and balance?',
    answers: ['Agility','Athletics','Dexterity','Acrobatics'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is not a damage type?',
    answers: ['Bludgeoning','Chopping','Force','Thunder'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the highest possible ability score that a character can have?',
    answers: ['Unlimited','20','18','30'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is not a condition?',
    answers: ['Invisible','Exhausted','Prone','Charmed'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  }, 
];